{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"410","question":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f :","option1":"10 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 1000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","option2":"20 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 10000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","option3":"20 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 2000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","option4":"20 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 20000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"567","question":"2013 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b ?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e","option3":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"451","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02 :","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d7e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d05\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4b","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d7b","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"498","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7e ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"635","question":"\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"649","question":"1889-\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d02","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"577","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u00a0\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"1994","option2":"1993","option3":"2001","option4":"1992","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"676","question":"2014 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02","option1":"\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48","option3":"\u0d15\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24","option4":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"160","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d2c\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","option1":"22","option2":"99","option3":"86","option4":"78","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"680","question":"\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f","option1":"\u0d12.\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d09\u0d37","option3":"\u0d37\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a","option4":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d2a\u0d3f .\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"1"}]},"code":"100"}
